(Armin) More than 100 years ago...
A natural enemy of humanity has appeared
between them and humans
There is an overwhelming difference in power...
Four
Humanity was soon on the brink of extinction.
Five
The surviving humans
Maria
Rose
Build Sheena's three walls
There, we achieved 100 years of peace.
Ten
but…
♪～
～♪
(Teacher) Until that time...
I am a completely greedy soul with no happiness.
Now as you see
For this reason he is punished here.
What greed does
We regret the sins of our souls
Appears to be pure
In this mountain in the first place
There is no punishment more bitter than this!
(Female) Ha ha ha...
twenty one
Hah... Ah!
twenty two
Ahhhhhhhhh
twenty three
Stop it! Let go!
twenty four
(Teacher) Oh, greed!
twenty five
Thou shalt draw my lineage unto thee.
(man shouts)
Ono gave meat to this.
As soon as he is forgotten,
What else should I do?
Ah, greed! My bloodline-
For you...
(Ellen) Ugh!
(Hannes) Ah!
Ellen what...
(Ellen) Almost there
I could have saved my mother!
Don't do unnecessary things!
I'll see my mother soon...
(Hannes) Don't worry!
(Eren) Ugh...
(Mikasa) Eren!
(Hannes) Ellen
You couldn't save your mother.
Because you didn't have the power
this!
(Hannes) I-
The reason I didn't stand up to the giant was...
Because I didn't have the courage!
Sorry
(Eren's sobs)
(Mikasa) Ah... again.
(Male) Wow!
Wow!
(Fugo) Hurry! Go to the inner gate!
on a ship anchored
Escape from Shiganshina!
hurry up! You'll be eaten alive!
(aluminum) located at key points on the wall
Districts that stand out like Shiganshina
Become a decoy to attract giants
Security costs and troops
played a role in suppressing
As per its role-
Targeted by giants
Residents of Shiganshina Ward
From just one inner gate
I had no choice but to escape
(garrison)
Everyone, throw away your bags!
Carry as many people as possible!
(Armin's grandfather)
Armin, sit down.
(Aluminum)
Eren and Mikasa are still...
Ah, it's here!
oh…
Ellen?
Leave him alone now
Poor thing
It doesn't look like that...
picture?
(Male) Ugh, wow!
(Fugo) How long have you been fidgeting?
hurry up!
What happened to the bullet?
Hurry! It's already in front of me!
(Male) That's a lie... something like this...
(Female) God... God...
(Residents murmur)
(Male) Hey! What are you doing?
(Garrison) It's full. Let's set sail.
(Female) Like that
Please give me a ride, even if it's just the kids
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Set sail!
(Female) Let me ride!
(Male) Get on it!
(Male) Uh... ugh.
(Male) Huh! Wow!
(Sound of a man falling into the sea)
(sound of cannon firing)
(Fugo) You idiot, where are you aiming?
(Soldier 1) But!
This guy has the precision to hit the target.
There isn't!
(Fugo) Now, such a promise is
It doesn't matter.
Hurry up and load the next bullet!
(Soldier 1) It's impossible!
ah…
(Soldier 2) The gate will close.
(Soldier 3) Retreat! You'll be left behind!
Hey!
(Hannes) Don't close it, wait a little longer.
There's still a lot of people left inside.
(Soldier 4) If you break through this gate...
One city becomes a giant
I'm not talking about being occupied.
Until the next wall, the area of human activity
Move back!
That's why the person in front of me
There's no reason to let it die
(Soldier 2) Close quickly!
(Soldier 3) The giant is coming!
Close the gate, hurry!
Away!
Wow... oh!
(Titan's footsteps)
Ha!
Ha…
Hey!
What…
that person
Huh, shoot!
What!
(Soldier 4) It doesn't work.
Ah... no! Hurry up and get to the gate!
(Fugo) It's coming! Evacuate!
one two three
A giant is coming! It's coming!
Hurry up to the gate!
(Hannes) The gate...
(Sound of giant breathing)
(Armin) South of Wall Maria
A few hours after the fall of Shiganshina District
The news is-
Every city in the human realm
spread in an instant
(Member 1) Is it true?
To Shiganshina
What do you mean the giants invaded?
(Member 1) I can't believe it...
Why did he change the wall after 100 years?
(Committee 2) Believe it or not.
There are people who actually escaped by boat.
Reports say he has 500 people on board.
(Chairman) The question is whether Shiganshina was the only one.
(Committee 3) But...
I think it's Wall Maria
There's no way they'll invade the inland area...
anyway-
Contact the center and ask for instructions
This kind of emergency
We can't deal with it alone.
(sound of door opening)
(Garrison) Excuse me!
Hayama just now...
Wall Maria is destroyed
It is said that a giant has invaded the inland area!
Is the end…
(Male) It's over...
Humanity will also be devoured by giants.
(Eren) It's over...
Already in that house of his...
I can never go back
Why-
Until the end, it's just a stupid verbal quarrel
I couldn't do it.
There's no more mother
she's nowhere to be found
Why!
(Hannes) Because you didn't have the strength.
Because I... humans are weak...
Do weak people have no choice but to cry?
(Eren) Those guys are from this world...
Ellen?
(Armin) What happened? Ellen
I'll destroy!
From this world-
Not one left!
Ellen...
(Armin) This year, the central government
The field of human activity-
To Wall Rose
decided to retreat
The person who was eaten by the giant the other day...
Approximately 10,000
(Grisha) Eren Carla Mikasa
Please stay safe
(Grisha) Ellen Ellen
Ellen!
(Ellen) Dad! Stop it, dad!
What are you trying to do?
(Grisha) Okay, just put your arm out.
(Ellen) I don't like it!
Her father died because her mother died.
It's gone crazy!
Ellen!
(Grisha) Let me go, dad!
(Grisha) It's for you!
(Ellen) What are you talking about?
(Grisha) Listen, don't forget your keys.
you have to reach
Someday I'll know the truth
Until then!
(bell sound)
Ha!
(Mikasa) Eren, are you okay?
I was bored
(Ellen) I think I met my father...
No way, it's a dream
(Ellen) I guess so...
(Mikasa) Let's go
There's food rationing
This used to be a food store.
Those who came by boat
He's all gathered here.
(Male) Hey, line him up properly!
(Male) Noise!
This is from her home
I haven't eaten anything!
we are still
I didn't survive.
(Armin) Eren Mikasa
(Eren) Armin
(Armin) Look, you're on time.
Because grandpa is for the child
she kept it for me
thank you
(Staff) Check
What? that person
I can't help it
We probably don't have enough rations for this number of people.
That's one day's worth
There are too many refugees
There's a lack of food to begin with...
those who live on the outside
You know it's not important, right?
(Attendant) Why did he do it for a stranger?
Our food?
If the giant had climbed over the wall anyway
eat more
I wish you could reduce it.
(Armin) What...
(Eren) Damn it!
Ah... Ellen!
This is a food shortage.
It's only going to get worse.
(Ellen) Ugh!
(Staff) It's it!
What is he doing, you brat?
(Ellen) Ugh, ah.
Even though I don't know
Even though I've never seen you before!
How does a giant...
shut up!
(Armin) I'm sorry.
hungry
Because I was irritated
So for adults
Such a rude thing...
I'm really sorry.
Geez…
You don't have to starve to death.
It's all thanks to us.
He's like that even as a kid.
You should have a feeling of gratitude
Yes
Damn it
Who will take care of those people?
He's going back to Wall Maria
Destroy all the giants!
Ellen
You're not serious, are you?
(Ellen) I'm serious!
I'm just trying to stay strong inside the walls
Different from those guys!
I don't need him like this!
Wow he is!
Ellen, I'm going to starve to death.
Don't you regret it?
That's what I've been blessed with.
I can't beat the giant!
(Armin) It's impossible, there's no way I can win.
we are
I have no choice but to live inside the walls
If you mess up, you'll die.
Like my father and mother
So he gave them
Are you going to pekopeko?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Now... I can't help it now!
It's just an excuse that it can't be helped
Then he'll be like that forever
Live like livestock!
Wimpy!
Ugh!
(Armin) Mikasa...
(Mikasa) If Armin is a wimp
Ellen and I are the same
we can run away from giants
Escape from the city
I haven't done anything myself
I even received help with food today.
A person without such power...
that giant
There's no way I can defeat even one of them.
The important thing is to survive
As my aunt said
(Ellen) Uh... uh...
mikasa
eat
I'll survive just fine
I won't let Eren starve to death.
(Eren's sobs)
(Armin) A few days later-
large numbers of refugees
To secure food
Sent to cultivate wasteland
However, food shortages are inevitable.
The following year, in 846, the central government
In the name of retaking Wall Maria
Injected a large number of refugees into the operation
250,000 people
It was equivalent to 20% of the population
He is one of only a hundred survivors.
With that sacrifice
Food shortages for those left behind
slightly improved
(Eren) It's all the Titan's fault.
If only I could crush them...
We can even take back our place
aluminum
I'm applying to be a training sergeant next year.
eh?
Gain strength to fight against giants
Me too…
Armin…
Me too!
(Mikasa) I'll go too.
Mikasa...you like him.
It's important to survive
I would have told you
Yes, that's why-
I'm going to keep you from dying
I understand, there are three of him.
(Keith) From now on, the 104th season
Holding the training corps induction ceremony
I'm unlucky
I will be supervising you.
It's Keith Shardis.
I have no intention of welcoming you.
You guys now-
At best, it can only become food for giants.
just livestock
They are lower than livestock.
You guys are of no use to such shit...
We spend three years training
I'll teach you how to fight giants!
Three years from now, when you guys stand in front of the giant
Is it just bait?
Or protect the king
Will it be a wall of honor?
or destroy the giants
A glorious soldier of humanity?
You guys decide!
(Ellen) Ah, I'll become it.
I will exterminate every single titan.
♪～
～♪