[RMJ] (Arumin) ima kara 100-nen ijō mae ―
[BAD-EN] (Armin) More than 100 years ago...
[RMJ] Jinrui ni aru tenteki ga arawareta
[BAD-EN] A natural enemy of humanity has appeared
[RMJ] Karera to jinrui no ma ni wa attōtekina chikara no sa ga sonzai shi ―
[BAD-EN] between them and humans
There is an overwhelming difference in power...
[RMJ] Tachimachi jinrui wa zetsumetsu no kiki o mukaeta
[BAD-EN] Humanity was soon on the brink of extinction.
[RMJ] Ikinokotta jinrui wa
[BAD-EN] The surviving humans
[RMJ] Maria
[BAD-EN] Maria
[RMJ] Rōze
[BAD-EN] Rose
[RMJ] Shīna no 3ttsu no kabe o kizuki
[BAD-EN] Build Sheena's three walls
[RMJ] Sokode 100-nen no heiwa o jitsugen sa seta
[BAD-EN] There, we achieved 100 years of peace.
[RMJ] Shikashi…
[BAD-EN] but…
[RMJ] ♪~
[BAD-EN] ♪～
[RMJ] ~♪
[BAD-EN] ～♪
[RMJ] (Kyōshi) ka no toki ni itaru made ―
[BAD-EN] (Teacher) Until that time...
[RMJ] Ga wa kō naki mattaku yokubukaki tamashīnariki
[BAD-EN] I am a completely greedy soul with no happiness.
[RMJ] Ima wa nanji (nanji) no mirugotoku
[BAD-EN] Now as you see
[RMJ] Ga ko no tame ni koko ni basse-raru
[BAD-EN] For this reason he is punished here.
[RMJ] Musabo (musabo)ri no nasu tokoro no koto wa
[BAD-EN] What greed does
[RMJ] Warera kuishi tamashī no tsumi o Shin muru-sama (sama) ni arawaru
[BAD-EN] We regret the sins of our souls
Appears to be pure
[RMJ] Somosomo kono yama ni kore yori nigaki batsu wa nashi!
[BAD-EN] In this mountain in the first place
There is no punishment more bitter than this!
[RMJ] (Josei) ha~a ha~a ha~a…
[BAD-EN] (Female) Ha ha ha...
[RMJ] Ha~tsu… a~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Hah... Ah!
[RMJ] Ākkyā~
[BAD-EN] Ahhhhhhhhh
[RMJ] Yamero ̄ ~tsu! Hanase ̄ ~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Stop it! Let go!
[RMJ] (Kyōshi) ā musabori yo!
[BAD-EN] (Teacher) Oh, greed!
[RMJ] Nanji waga chisuji o nanji no moto (moto) ni hikite
[BAD-EN] Thou shalt draw my lineage unto thee.
[RMJ] (Dansei no sakebigoe)
[BAD-EN] (man shouts)
[RMJ] Kore ni onore (ono) ga niku o sa e
[RMJ] (Dansei no sakebigoe)
[BAD-EN] (man shouts)
[RMJ] Kaerimi zara shimeshi hodo nareba
[BAD-EN] As soon as he is forgotten,
[RMJ] Kono ue nani o subeki ya!
[BAD-EN] What else should I do?
[RMJ] Āmmusabori yo! Waga chisuji o ―
[BAD-EN] Ah, greed! My bloodline-
[RMJ] Nanji no moto ni…
[BAD-EN] For you...
[RMJ] (Eren) ū! (Han'nesu) a~tsu!
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Ugh!
(Hannes) Ah!
[RMJ] Eren nani o…
[BAD-EN] Ellen what...
[RMJ] (Eren) mōsukoshi de kāsan o tasuke raretanoni!
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Almost there
I could have saved my mother!
[RMJ] Yokeina koto sun janē yo!
[BAD-EN] Don't do unnecessary things!
[RMJ] Mōsukoshi de kāsan o…
[BAD-EN] I'll see my mother soon...
[RMJ] (Han'nesu) īkagen ni shiro!
[BAD-EN] (Hannes) Don't worry!
[RMJ] (Eren) ū ~tsu…
[BAD-EN] (Eren) Ugh...
[RMJ] (Mikasa) eren!
[BAD-EN] (Mikasa) Eren!
[RMJ] (Han'nesu) eren
[BAD-EN] (Hannes) Ellen
[RMJ] Omae ga kāsan o tasuke rarenakatta no wa
[BAD-EN] You couldn't save your mother.
[RMJ] Omae ni chikara ga nakattakarada
[BAD-EN] Because you didn't have the power
[RMJ] Kono!
[BAD-EN] this!
[RMJ] (Han'nesu) ore ga ―
[BAD-EN] (Hannes) I-
[RMJ] Ore ga Kyojin ni tachimukawanakatta no wa ―
[BAD-EN] The reason I didn't stand up to the giant was...
[RMJ] Ore ni yūki ga nakattakarada!
[BAD-EN] Because I didn't have the courage!
[RMJ] Sumanai
[BAD-EN] Sorry
[RMJ] (Eren no susurinaki)
[BAD-EN] (Eren's sobs)
[RMJ] (Mikasa) ā… ma tada
[BAD-EN] (Mikasa) Ah... again.
[RMJ] (Dansei) uwa a~
[BAD-EN] (Male) Wow!
[RMJ] Uwa ā a ̄ ~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Wow!
[RMJ] (Fūgo) isoge! Uchikado e ike!
[BAD-EN] (Fugo) Hurry! Go to the inner gate!
[RMJ] Teihaku shite iru fune de shiganshina o dasshutsu suru nda!
[BAD-EN] on a ship anchored
Escape from Shiganshina!
[RMJ] Hayakushiro! Kui korosa reru zo!
[BAD-EN] hurry up! You'll be eaten alive!
[RMJ] (Arumin) kabe no yōsho yōsho ni aru shiganshina no yō ni tosshutsu shita chiku wa
[BAD-EN] (aluminum) located at key points on the wall
Districts that stand out like Shiganshina
[RMJ] Kyojin o hikitsukeru otori (o Tori) to nari
[BAD-EN] Become a decoy to attract giants
[RMJ] Keibi no kosuto to heiryoku o osaeru yakuwari o hatashite ita
[BAD-EN] Security costs and troops
played a role in suppressing
[RMJ] Sono yakuwari-dōri ―
[BAD-EN] As per its role-
[RMJ] Kyojin-tachi no hyōteki to natta shiganshina-ku no jūnin-tachi wa
[BAD-EN] Targeted by giants
Residents of Shiganshina Ward
[RMJ] Tatta 1tsu no Uchikado kara dasshutsu suru shika nakatta
[BAD-EN] From just one inner gate
I had no choice but to escape
[RMJ] (Chūton-hei) zen'in nimotsu o sutero!
[BAD-EN] (garrison)
Everyone, throw away your bags!
[RMJ] 1-Ri demo ōku noseru nda!
[BAD-EN] Carry as many people as possible!
[RMJ] (Arumin no sofu) arumin suwatte nasai
[BAD-EN] (Armin's grandfather)
Armin, sit down.
[RMJ] (Arumin) demo eren to mikasa ga mada…
[BAD-EN] (Aluminum)
Eren and Mikasa are still...
[RMJ] Akkita!
[BAD-EN] Ah, it's here!
[RMJ] O…
[BAD-EN] oh…
[RMJ] Eren?
[BAD-EN] Ellen?
[RMJ] Ima wa yamete oki nasai
[BAD-EN] Leave him alone now
[RMJ] Kawaisō ni ano yōsu ja yoppodo…
[BAD-EN] Poor thing
It doesn't look like that...
[RMJ] E?
[BAD-EN] picture?
[RMJ] (Dansei) ū wwā!
[BAD-EN] (Male) Ugh, wow!
[RMJ] (Fūgo) nani motamota shite nda hayakushiro!
[BAD-EN] (Fugo) How long have you been fidgeting?
hurry up!
[RMJ] Hōdan wa dō shita?
[BAD-EN] What happened to the bullet?
[RMJ] I… isoge! Mō me no maeda zo!
[BAD-EN] Hurry! It's already in front of me!
[RMJ] (Dansei) usodaro… Konna koto tte…
[BAD-EN] (Male) That's a lie... something like this...
[RMJ] (Josei) kamisama… kamisama…
[BAD-EN] (Female) God... God...
[RMJ] (Jūmin-tachi no zawameki)
[BAD-EN] (Residents murmur)
[RMJ] (Dansei) oi! Nani sunda!
[BAD-EN] (Male) Hey! What are you doing?
[RMJ] (Chūton-hei) mō man'inda shukkō suru
[BAD-EN] (Garrison) It's full. Let's set sail.
[RMJ] (Josei) son'na onegai nosete kodomo dake demo
[BAD-EN] (Female) Like that
Please give me a ride, even if it's just the kids
[RMJ] Sumanēga murida
[BAD-EN] I'm sorry, but I can't.
[RMJ] Shukkō!
[BAD-EN] Set sail!
[RMJ] (Josei) nosete! (Dansei) nosero!
[BAD-EN] (Female) Let me ride!
(Male) Get on it!
[RMJ] (Dansei) u… ū ~
[BAD-EN] (Male) Uh... ugh.
[RMJ] (Dansei) n ~tsu! Uwa ̄ ~tsu!
[BAD-EN] (Male) Huh! Wow!
[RMJ] (Dansei ga umi ni ochiru oto)
[BAD-EN] (Sound of a man falling into the sea)
[RMJ] (Taihōwoutsu-on)
[BAD-EN] (sound of cannon firing)
[RMJ] (Fūgo) baka yarō doko neratte nda
[BAD-EN] (Fugo) You idiot, where are you aiming?
[RMJ] (Heishi 1) shikashi!
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 1) But!
[RMJ] Koitsu ni mato o neraeru seido nanka arimasen yo!
[BAD-EN] This guy has the precision to hit the target.
There isn't!
[RMJ] (Fūgo) ima son'na gotaku (go Taku) wa dō demo ī nda yo
[BAD-EN] (Fugo) Now, such a promise is
It doesn't matter.
[RMJ] Hayaku tsugi no dan komero!
[BAD-EN] Hurry up and load the next bullet!
[RMJ] (Heishi 1) murida!
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 1) It's impossible!
[RMJ] Ā…
[BAD-EN] ah…
[RMJ] (Heishi 2) mon ga shimaru zo
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 2) The gate will close.
[RMJ] (Heishi 3) tettaida torinokosa reru zo!
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 3) Retreat! You'll be left behind!
[RMJ] Oi!
[BAD-EN] Hey!
[RMJ] (Han'nesu) shimeru na mōsukoshi mate
[BAD-EN] (Hannes) Don't close it, wait a little longer.
[RMJ] Mada-chū ni taisei no hito ga nokotteru nda zo
[BAD-EN] There's still a lot of people left inside.
[RMJ] (Heishi 4) kono mon o toppa sa retara ―
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 4) If you break through this gate...
[RMJ] Machi hitotsu ga Kyojin ni senkyo sa reta dokoro no hanashi janai
[BAD-EN] One city becomes a giant
I'm not talking about being occupied.
[RMJ] -Ji no kabe made jinrui no katsudō ryōiki ga kōtai suru nda zo!
[BAD-EN] Until the next wall, the area of human activity
Move back!
[RMJ] Dakaratte me no mae no ningen o migoroshi ni suru riyū wa nai
[BAD-EN] That's why the person in front of me
There's no reason to let it die
[RMJ] (Heishi 2) hayaku shimero!
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 2) Close quickly!
[RMJ] (Heishi 3) Kyojin ga kuru zo!
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 3) The giant is coming!
[RMJ] Heimon isoge!
[BAD-EN] Close the gate, hurry!
[RMJ] Yose!
[BAD-EN] Away!
[RMJ] U wa~tsuo… oi!
[BAD-EN] Wow... oh!
[RMJ] (Kyojin no ashioto) ha~tsu!
[BAD-EN] (Titan's footsteps)
Ha!
[RMJ] (Kyojin no ashioto)
[BAD-EN] (Titan's footsteps)
[RMJ] Ha~tsu…
[BAD-EN] Ha…
[RMJ] Hi~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Hey!
[RMJ] Nanda…
[BAD-EN] What…
[RMJ] Aitsu
[BAD-EN] that person
[RMJ] Ha~a~tsuute ̄ ~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Huh, shoot!
[RMJ] Nani ~tsu!
[BAD-EN] What!
[RMJ] (Heishi 4) kikanai
[BAD-EN] (Soldier 4) It doesn't work.
[RMJ] Ā… dameda hayaku mon o!
[BAD-EN] Ah... no! Hurry up and get to the gate!
[RMJ] (Fūgo) kuru zo! Taihi!
[BAD-EN] (Fugo) It's coming! Evacuate!
[RMJ] Kyojin ga kuru zo! Tsukkonde kuru!
[BAD-EN] A giant is coming! It's coming!
[RMJ] Hayaku mon o!
[BAD-EN] Hurry up to the gate!
[RMJ] (Han'nesu) mon ga…
[BAD-EN] (Hannes) The gate...
[RMJ] (Kyojin ga ikiwohaku-on)
[BAD-EN] (Sound of giant breathing)
[RMJ] (Arumin) u~ōru Maria nanpō
[BAD-EN] (Armin) South of Wall Maria
[RMJ] Shiganshina-ku kanraku kara sūjikango ―
[BAD-EN] A few hours after the fall of Shiganshina District
[RMJ] Sono shirase wa ―
[BAD-EN] The news is-
[RMJ] Jinrui ryōiki-nai no arayuru machi ni matatakumani hiromatta
[BAD-EN] Every city in the human realm
spread in an instant
[RMJ] (Iin 1) hontōnanoka?
[BAD-EN] (Member 1) Is it true?
[RMJ] Shiganshina ni Kyojin ga shin'nyū shita to iu no wa?
[BAD-EN] To Shiganshina
What do you mean the giants invaded?
[RMJ] (Iin 1) shinji rare n…
[BAD-EN] (Member 1) I can't believe it...
[RMJ] 100-Nen motta kabe ga naze ima ni natte?
[BAD-EN] Why did he change the wall after 100 years?
[RMJ] (Iin 2) shinjiru mo shinjinai mo gen'ni fune de dasshutsu shite kita ningen ga iru nda
[BAD-EN] (Committee 2) Believe it or not.
There are people who actually escaped by boat.
[RMJ] Hōkoku ja 500-ri wa notte irurashī
[BAD-EN] Reports say he has 500 people on board.
[RMJ] (Iin-chō) mondai wa shiganshina dake de sunda no ka dō ka
[BAD-EN] (Chairman) The question is whether Shiganshina was the only one.
[RMJ] (Iin 3) shikashi…
[BAD-EN] (Committee 3) But...
[RMJ] Masaka u~ōru Maria no naichi ni made shin'nyū sa reru hazu wa…
[BAD-EN] I think it's Wall Maria
There's no way they'll invade the inland area...
[RMJ] Tonikaku ―
[BAD-EN] anyway-
[RMJ] Chūō ni renraku shite shiji o aogu
[BAD-EN] Contact the center and ask for instructions
[RMJ] Kon'na kinkyū jitai wa totemo wareware dakede wa taisho dekin
[BAD-EN] This kind of emergency
We can't deal with it alone.
[RMJ] (Doa no hiraku oto) (chūton-hei) shitsureishimasu!
[BAD-EN] (sound of door opening)
(Garrison) Excuse me!
[RMJ] Tattaima hayauma ga…
[BAD-EN] Hayama just now...
[RMJ] U~ōru Maria ga yabura re naichi ni Kyojin ga shin'nyū shita to no kotodesu!
[BAD-EN] Wall Maria is destroyed
It is said that a giant has invaded the inland area!
[RMJ] Owarida…
[BAD-EN] Is the end…
[RMJ] (Dansei) owarida…
[BAD-EN] (Male) It's over...
[RMJ] Mata jinrui wa Kyojin ni kui tsukusa reru
[BAD-EN] Humanity will also be devoured by giants.
[RMJ] (Eren) owari…
[BAD-EN] (Eren) It's over...
[RMJ] Mō ano ie ni wa ―
[BAD-EN] Already in that house of his...
[RMJ] Nidoto kaerenai
[BAD-EN] I can never go back
[RMJ] Dōshite ―
[BAD-EN] Why-
[RMJ] Saigomade ro kude mo nai kuchi genka shika dekinakatta nda
[BAD-EN] Until the end, it's just a stupid verbal quarrel
I couldn't do it.
[RMJ] Mō kāsan wa inai
[BAD-EN] There's no more mother
[RMJ] Dokoni mo inai
[BAD-EN] she's nowhere to be found
[RMJ] Dōshite!
[BAD-EN] Why!
[RMJ] (Han'nesu) omaeni-ryoku ga nakattakarada
[BAD-EN] (Hannes) Because you didn't have the strength.
[RMJ] Ore ga… ningen ga yowaikara ―
[BAD-EN] Because I... humans are weak...
[RMJ] Yowai yatsu wa naku shika nai no ka?
[BAD-EN] Do weak people have no choice but to cry?
[RMJ] (Eren) aitsu-ra konoyo kara…
[BAD-EN] (Eren) Those guys are from this world...
[RMJ] Eren?
[BAD-EN] Ellen?
[RMJ] (Arumin)-dōshita no? Eren
[BAD-EN] (Armin) What happened? Ellen
[RMJ] Eren?
[BAD-EN] Ellen?
[RMJ] Kuchiku shite yaru!
[BAD-EN] I'll destroy!
[RMJ] Konoyo kara ―
[BAD-EN] From this world-
[RMJ] 1-Biki nokorazu!
[BAD-EN] Not one left!
[RMJ] Eren…
[BAD-EN] Ellen...
[RMJ] (Arumin) kono-nen chūō seifu wa jinrui no katsudō ryōiki o ―
[BAD-EN] (Armin) This year, the central government
The field of human activity-
[RMJ] U~ōru rōze made kōtai sa seru koto o kettei shita
[BAD-EN] To Wall Rose
decided to retreat
[RMJ] Konoaida Kyojin ni kuwa reta mono wa ―
[BAD-EN] The person who was eaten by the giant the other day...
[RMJ] Oyoso 1 man ni mo oyonda
[BAD-EN] Approximately 10,000
[RMJ] (Gurisha) eren Karura mikasa
[BAD-EN] (Grisha) Eren Carla Mikasa
[RMJ] Bujide ite kure
[BAD-EN] Please stay safe
[RMJ] (Gurisha) eren eren
[BAD-EN] (Grisha) Ellen Ellen
[RMJ] Eren!
[BAD-EN] Ellen!
[RMJ] (Eren) tōsan! Yamete yo tōsan!
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Dad! Stop it, dad!
[RMJ] Nan o shiyou to shi teru no?
[BAD-EN] What are you trying to do?
[RMJ] (Gurisha) īkara ude o dashi nasai
[BAD-EN] (Grisha) Okay, just put your arm out.
[RMJ] (Eren) iyada!
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) I don't like it!
[RMJ] Tōsan wa kāsan ga shinde okashiku natta nda!
[BAD-EN] Her father died because her mother died.
It's gone crazy!
[RMJ] Eren!
[BAD-EN] Ellen!
[RMJ] (Gurisha) hanashite yo tōsan!
[BAD-EN] (Grisha) Let me go, dad!
[RMJ] (Gurisha) omae no tamena nda!
[BAD-EN] (Grisha) It's for you!
[RMJ] (Eren) nani o itteru no?
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) What are you talking about?
[RMJ] (Gurisha) ī ka kagi o wasureruna
[BAD-EN] (Grisha) Listen, don't forget your keys.
[RMJ] Omae wa Tadoru (tado)ri tsukanakereba naranai
[BAD-EN] you have to reach
[RMJ] Itsuka shinjitsu ga wakaru
[BAD-EN] Someday I'll know the truth
[RMJ] Sono toki made!
[BAD-EN] Until then!
[RMJ] (Kanenone) ha~tsu!
[BAD-EN] (bell sound)
Ha!
[RMJ] (Mikasa) eren daijōbu? Unasare teta
[BAD-EN] (Mikasa) Eren, are you okay?
I was bored
[RMJ] (Eren) tōsan to atteta ki ga suru…
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) I think I met my father...
[RMJ] Masaka yumeda yo
[BAD-EN] No way, it's a dream
[RMJ] (Eren) sō ka na…
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) I guess so...
[RMJ] (Mikasa) yukō
[BAD-EN] (Mikasa) Let's go
[RMJ] Shokuryō no haikyū ga aru tte
[BAD-EN] There's food rationing
[RMJ] Koko shokuryō-kodattatte
[BAD-EN] This used to be a food store.
[RMJ] Fune de kita hito wa min'na koko ni atsume rare teru
[BAD-EN] Those who came by boat
He's all gathered here.
[RMJ] (Dansei) oi chanto narabe!
[BAD-EN] (Male) Hey, line him up properly!
[RMJ] (Dansei) uru se e!
[BAD-EN] (Male) Noise!
[RMJ] Kotchi wa yūbe kara nani mo kuttenē nda!
[BAD-EN] This is from her home
I haven't eaten anything!
[RMJ] Watashitachi wa mada ikinokotta wake janai
[BAD-EN] we are still
I didn't survive.
[RMJ] (Arumin) eren mikasa
[BAD-EN] (Armin) Eren Mikasa
[RMJ] (Eren) arumin
[BAD-EN] (Eren) Armin
[RMJ] (Arumin) hora maniatta yo
[BAD-EN] (Armin) Look, you're on time.
[RMJ] Ojīchan ga kodomo no bundakara tte morattoite kureta nda
[BAD-EN] Because grandpa is for the child
she kept it for me
[RMJ] Arigatō
[BAD-EN] thank you
[RMJ] (Kakariin) che~
[BAD-EN] (Staff) Check
[RMJ] Nanda? Aitsu
[BAD-EN] What? that person
[RMJ] Shikata (shikata) nai yo
[BAD-EN] I can't help it
[RMJ] Kono haikyū tabun ninzū-bun nai nda
[BAD-EN] We probably don't have enough rations for this number of people.
[RMJ] Sore ga 1-nichi-bun datte
[BAD-EN] That's one day's worth
[RMJ] Hinan-min ga ō sugiru nda
[BAD-EN] There are too many refugees
[RMJ] Motomoto shokuryō fusokudashi ―
[BAD-EN] There's a lack of food to begin with...
[RMJ] Sotogawa ni sunde iru hito hodo daiji ni sa renai no wa shitterudesho?
[BAD-EN] those who live on the outside
You know it's not important, right?
[RMJ] (Kakariin) nani de yosomono (Mon) no tame ni oretachi no shokuryō o?
[BAD-EN] (Attendant) Why did he do it for a stranger?
Our food?
[RMJ] Dōse Kyojin ga kabe o koeta n'nara
[BAD-EN] If the giant had climbed over the wall anyway
[RMJ] Motto kutte herashite kurerya yokatta nda yo
[BAD-EN] eat more
I wish you could reduce it.
[RMJ] (Arumin) na~tsu… (eren) ku~tsu!
[BAD-EN] (Armin) What...
(Eren) Damn it!
[RMJ] A… eren!
[BAD-EN] Ah... Ellen!
[RMJ] Kore ja shokuryōbusoku ga hidoku naru ippōda ze
[BAD-EN] This is a food shortage.
It's only going to get worse.
[RMJ] (Eren) ū ~tsu! (Kakariin) ite~tsu!
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Ugh!
(Staff) It's it!
[RMJ] Nan sunda kono gaki!
[BAD-EN] What is he doing, you brat?
[RMJ] (Eren) u~tsua~
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Ugh, ah.
[RMJ] Shiranai kuse ni
[BAD-EN] Even though I don't know
[RMJ] Omae nanka mita koto mo nai kuse ni!
[BAD-EN] Even though I've never seen you before!
[RMJ] Kyojin ga dō yatte hito o…
[BAD-EN] How does a giant...
[RMJ] Uru se e!
[BAD-EN] shut up!
[RMJ] (Arumin) gomen'nasai ~
[BAD-EN] (Armin) I'm sorry.
[RMJ] Onaka ga suite iraira shi tetakara
[BAD-EN] hungry
Because I was irritated
[RMJ] Dakaraotona no hito ni kon'na shitsureina koto o…
[BAD-EN] So for adults
Such a rude thing...
[RMJ] Honto gomen'nasai ~
[BAD-EN] I'm really sorry.
[RMJ] Ttaku…
[BAD-EN] Geez…
[RMJ] Omaetachi ga uejini shinaide sumu no mo oretachi no okagena nda zo
[BAD-EN] You don't have to starve to death.
It's all thanks to us.
[RMJ] Kodomo datte sore kurai no kanshanokimochi wa motsu monda
[BAD-EN] He's like that even as a kid.
You should have a feeling of gratitude
[RMJ] Wa i~
[BAD-EN] Yes
[RMJ] Kuso~
[BAD-EN] Damn it
[RMJ] Dare ga an'na yatsura no sewa ni naru ka!
[BAD-EN] Who will take care of those people?
[RMJ] Modotte yaru u~ōru Maria ni
[BAD-EN] He's going back to Wall Maria
[RMJ] Kyojin nanka zenbu buttsubushite!
[BAD-EN] Destroy all the giants!
[RMJ] Eren honki de itteru n janai yo ne?
[BAD-EN] Ellen
You're not serious, are you?
[RMJ] (Eren) honkida!
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) I'm serious!
[RMJ] Ore wa kabe no naka de tsuyogatteru dake no aitsu-ra to wa chigau!
[BAD-EN] I'm just trying to stay strong inside the walls
Different from those guys!
[RMJ] Konna mon iranai!
[BAD-EN] I don't need him like this!
[RMJ] Wa~tsuā~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Wow he is!
[RMJ] Eren uejini shi chau yo
[BAD-EN] Ellen, I'm going to starve to death.
[RMJ] Omae kuyashikunai no ka yo?
[BAD-EN] Don't you regret it?
[RMJ] Son'na mon megunde moratterukara Kyojin ni katenai nda!
[BAD-EN] That's what I've been blessed with.
I can't beat the giant!
[RMJ] (Arumin) muridayo kateru wake nai
[BAD-EN] (Armin) It's impossible, there's no way I can win.
[RMJ] Bokutachi wa kabe no naka de ikiru shika nai nda
[BAD-EN] we are
I have no choice but to live inside the walls
[RMJ] Mucha o sureba shinu boku no tōsan kāsan mitai ni
[BAD-EN] If you mess up, you'll die.
Like my father and mother
[RMJ] Dakaraaitsu-ra ni pekopeko suru no ka?
[BAD-EN] So he gave them
Are you going to pekopeko?
[RMJ] Hazukashikunai no ka yo?
[BAD-EN] Aren't you embarrassed?
[RMJ] Ima wa… ima wa shōganai yo!
[BAD-EN] Now... I can't help it now!
[RMJ] Shōganai nante iiwakeda
[BAD-EN] It's just an excuse that it can't be helped
[RMJ] Dattaraitsu made mo sō yatte kachiku mitai ni ikiro!
[BAD-EN] Then he'll be like that forever
Live like livestock!
[RMJ] Yowamushi!
[BAD-EN] Wimpy!
[RMJ] U~tsu!
[BAD-EN] Ugh!
[RMJ] (Arumin) mikasa…
[BAD-EN] (Armin) Mikasa...
[RMJ] (Mikasa) arumin ga yowamushinara eren to watashi mo onaji
[BAD-EN] (Mikasa) If Armin is a wimp
Ellen and I are the same
[RMJ] Watashitachiha Kyojin kara nigeru no mo machi kara nigeru no mo
[BAD-EN] we can run away from giants
Escape from the city
[RMJ] Nan hitotsu jibun de yatte inai
[BAD-EN] I haven't done anything myself
[RMJ] Kyō taberu mono sae tasukete moratta
[BAD-EN] I even received help with food today.
[RMJ] Son'na chikara no nai ningen ga ―
[BAD-EN] A person without such power...
[RMJ] Ano kyojin o 1-biki datte taoseru wake nai
[BAD-EN] that giant
There's no way I can defeat even one of them.
[RMJ] Taisetsuna no wa ikinobiru koto
[BAD-EN] The important thing is to survive
[RMJ] Obasan ga itteta tōri
[BAD-EN] As my aunt said
[RMJ] (Eren) u… u…
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Uh... uh...
[RMJ] Mikasa
[BAD-EN] mikasa
[RMJ] Tabete chanto ikinokoru no
[BAD-EN] eat
I'll survive just fine
[RMJ] Eren o uejini nanka sasenai
[BAD-EN] I won't let Eren starve to death.
[RMJ] (Eren no susurinaki)
[BAD-EN] (Eren's sobs)
[RMJ] (Arumin) sūjitsugo ―
[BAD-EN] (Armin) A few days later-
[RMJ] Tairyō no hinan-min-tachi wa
[BAD-EN] large numbers of refugees
[RMJ] Shokuryō kakuho no tame arechi no kaitaku ni mawasa reta
[BAD-EN] To secure food
Sent to cultivate wasteland
[RMJ] Shikashi shokuryōnan wa yoke rarezu ―
[BAD-EN] However, food shortages are inevitable.
[RMJ] Yokunen no 846-nen chūō seifu wa u~ōru Maria dakkan o meimoku ni
[BAD-EN] The following year, in 846, the central government
In the name of retaking Wall Maria
[RMJ] Tairyō no hinan-min o sakusen ni tōnyū shita
[BAD-EN] Injected a large number of refugees into the operation
[RMJ] Sono sū 25 man-ri
[BAD-EN] 250,000 people
[RMJ] Jinkō no 2-wari ni sōtō shitaga seizon-sha wa wazuka 百数十名
[BAD-EN] It was equivalent to 20% of the population
He is one of only a hundred survivors.
[RMJ] Sono gisei de nokosa reta hitobito no shokuryōbusoku wa
[BAD-EN] With that sacrifice
Food shortages for those left behind
[RMJ] Wazukanagara ni kaizen sa reta
[BAD-EN] slightly improved
[RMJ] (Eren) zenbu Kyojin no seida
[BAD-EN] (Eren) It's all the Titan's fault.
[RMJ] Aitsu-ra sae 叩 (Tata)ki tsubuseba ―
[BAD-EN] If only I could crush them...
[RMJ] Oretachi no ibasho datte torimodoseru
[BAD-EN] We can even take back our place
[RMJ] Arumin
[BAD-EN] aluminum
[RMJ] Ore wa rainen kunren-hei ni shigan suru
[BAD-EN] I'm applying to be a training sergeant next year.
[RMJ] E~tsu?
[BAD-EN] eh?
[RMJ] Kyojin to tatakau chikara o tsukeru
[BAD-EN] Gain strength to fight against giants
[RMJ] Boku mo…
[BAD-EN] Me too…
[RMJ] Arumin…
[BAD-EN] Armin…
[RMJ] Boku mo!
[BAD-EN] Me too!
[RMJ] (Mikasa) watashi mo ikou
[BAD-EN] (Mikasa) I'll go too.
[RMJ] Mikasa… omae wa ī nda zo
[BAD-EN] Mikasa...you like him.
[RMJ] Ikinobiru koto ga daiji tte ittetarou
[BAD-EN] It's important to survive
I would have told you
[RMJ] -Sōdakara ―
[BAD-EN] Yes, that's why-
[RMJ] Anata o shina senai tame ni iku
[BAD-EN] I'm going to keep you from dying
[RMJ] Wakatta 3-ri de
[BAD-EN] I understand, there are three of him.
[RMJ] (Kīsu) tadaima yori dai 104-ki kunren heidan no nyūdan-shiki o okonau
[BAD-EN] (Keith) From now on, the 104th season
Holding the training corps induction ceremony
[RMJ] Watashi ga unwaruku kisama-ra o kantoku suru koto ni natta
[BAD-EN] I'm unlucky
I will be supervising you.
[RMJ] Kīsu shādisuda
[BAD-EN] It's Keith Shardis.
[RMJ] Kisama-ra o kangei suru ki wa mōtō nai
[BAD-EN] I have no intention of welcoming you.
[RMJ] Ima no kisama-ra wa ―
[BAD-EN] You guys now-
[RMJ] Seizei Kyojin no esa ni naru shika nai tada no kachiku
[BAD-EN] At best, it can only become food for giants.
just livestock
[RMJ] Kachiku ika no sonzaida
[BAD-EN] They are lower than livestock.
[RMJ] Son'na kuso no yaku ni mo tatan kisama-ra o ―
[BAD-EN] You guys are of no use to such shit...
[RMJ] Wareware ga 3-nen kakete kitaeageru
[BAD-EN] We spend three years training
[RMJ] Kyojin to tatakau jutsu o tatakikonde yaru!
[BAD-EN] I'll teach you how to fight giants!
[RMJ] 3-Nen-go kisama-ra ga Kyojin no mae ni tatta toki
[BAD-EN] Three years from now, when you guys stand in front of the giant
[RMJ] Tada no esa no mama ka ―
[BAD-EN] Is it just bait?
[RMJ] Aruiwa ō o mamoru meiyo aru kabe to naru ka
[BAD-EN] Or protect the king
Will it be a wall of honor?
[RMJ] Matawa kyojin o kuchiku suru eikō aru jinrui no heishi ka
[BAD-EN] or destroy the giants
A glorious soldier of humanity?
[RMJ] Kisama-ra ga kimero!
[BAD-EN] You guys decide!
[RMJ] (Eren) ā ore wa naru
[BAD-EN] (Ellen) Ah, I'll become it.
[RMJ] Kyojin o 1-biki nokorazu kuchiku shite yaru
[BAD-EN] I will exterminate every single titan.
[RMJ] ♪~
[BAD-EN] ♪～
[RMJ] ~♪
[BAD-EN] ～♪